let questions = [
   
    // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
    // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
      {
      numb: 1,
      question: "What domain deals with microcontrollers?",
      answer: "Embedded Systems Development",
      options: [
        "Back-end Development",
        "Data Science",
        "Embedded Systems Development", 
        "API Development "
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of these is not a core data type in Python?",
        answer: "Class",
        options: [
          "List",
          "Dictionary",
          "Turple",
          "Class"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following is a Python tuple?",
        answer: "(1,2,3,4,)",
        options: [
          "[1,2,3,4,]",
          "(1,2,3,4,)",
          "{1,2,3,4,}",
          "{}"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which is the most used programming language?",
        answer: "JavaScript",
        options: [
          "C language",
          "Python",
          "Java",
          "JavaScript"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which programming language is used by Flutter Developers?",
        answer: "Dart",
        options: [
          "C#",
          "Nail",
          "Ruby",
          "Dart"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which one is not a flutter state management?",
        answer: "Dart",
        options: [
          "GetX",
          "Dart",
          "Block",
          "Provider"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The language that programmers create and use to tell a computer what to do.?",
        answer: "Code",
        options: [
          "Program",
          "Condition",
          "Function",
          "Code"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 8,
        question: "An algorithm that has been coded into something that can be run by a machine?",
        answer: "Program",
        options: [
          "Debuggin",
          "Program",
          "Iterating",
          "Function"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Statements that only run under certain conditions?",
        answer: "Conditional",
        options: [
          "Output",
          "Conditional",
          "Iterating",
          "Debugging"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Mistakes, usually made by the human who wrote the code?",
        answer: "Bugs",
        options: [
          "Loop",
          "Bugs",
          "Code",
          "Statement"
        ]
      },
    ];